<resources>
    <string name="app_name">pr11_deepsea</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="title_secrecy">Secrecy</string>
    <string name="title_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="default_web_client_id">414320372365-7gdugqp55opjd92b6on96nfp0ts877v0.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>


    <string name="extercise">Regular physical activity can boost mood and reduce stress.</string>
    <string name="meditation">Practices like meditation and mindfulness can help calm the mind and promote relaxation. </string>
    <string name="naturetime">Being outdoors, whether it is a walk in the park or a hike in the mountains, can have a positive impact on mental well-being.</string>
    <string name="creativity">Engaging in creative activities like painting, writing, or playing music can be therapeutic and provide a sense of accomplishment. </string>
    <string name="socializing0">Engaging in creative activities like painting, writing, or playing music can be therapeutic and provide a sense of accomplishment. </string>
    <string name="eating"> A balanced diet rich in fruits, vegetables, and whole grains can support overall well-being. </string>
    <string name="sleep">Prioritize good sleep hygiene to ensure adequate rest, as lack of sleep can negatively affect mental health. </string>

    <string name="title_activity">Activity</string>
    <string name="title_appointment">Appointment</string>
    <string name="title_test">Tests</string>


    <string name="take_test">Take Test</string>
    <string name="anxiety">Anxiety</string>
    <string name="depression">Depression</string>
    <string name="autism">Autism</string>
    <string name="suicidality">Suicidality</string>
    <string name="eating_disorder">Eating Disorder</string>
    <string name="dissociation">Dissociation</string>
    <string name="adhd">ADHD</string>
    <string name="testSleep">Sleep</string>
    <string name="not_at_all">Not at all</string>
    <string name="several_days">Several days</string>
    <string name="more_than_half_the_days">More than half the days</string>
    <string name="nearly_everyday">Nearly everyday</string>
    <string name="autism_test">Autism Test</string>


    <string name="AnxietyQuestionTitle">Anxiety test</string>
    <string name="AnxietyQuestion1">1. Feeling nervous, anxious, or on edge</string>
    <string name="AnxietyQuestion2">2. Not being able to stop or control worrying</string>
    <string name="AnxietyQuestion3">3. Worrying too much about different things</string>
    <string name="AnxietyQuestion4">4. Trouble relaxing</string>
    <string name="QuestionsSubmit">Submit</string>
    <string name="AnxietyQuestion5">5. Being so restless that it is hard to sit still</string>
    <string name="AnxietyQuestion6">6. Becoming easily annoyed or irritable</string>
    <string name="AnxietyQuestion7">7. Feeling afraid, as if something awful might happen</string>


    <string name="DepressionTestTitle">Depression Test</string>
    <string name="DepressionQuestion1">1. Little interest or pleasure in doing things</string>
    <string name="DepressionQuestion2">2. Feeling down, depressed, or hopeless</string>
    <string name="DepressionQuestion3">3. Trouble falling or staying asleep, or sleeping too much</string>
    <string name="DepressionQuestion4">4. Feeling tired or having little energy</string>
    <string name="DepressionQuestion5">5. Poor appetite or overeating</string>
    <string name="DepressionQuestion6">6. Feeling bad about yourself - or that you are a failure or have let yourself or your family down</string>
    <string name="DepressionQuestion7">7. Trouble concentrating on things, such as reading the newspaper or watching television</string>


    <string name="PersonalityDisorderTestTitle">Personality Disorder Test</string>
    <string name="PersonalityQuestion1">1. My emotions change very quickly, and I experience intense episodes of sadness, irritability, and anxiety or panic attacks.</string>
    <string name="PersonalityQuestion2">2. My level of anger is often inappropriate, intense, and difficult to control.</string>
    <string name="PersonalityQuestion3">3. Now, or in the past, when upset, I have engaged in recurrent suicidal behaviors, gestures, threats, or self-injurious behavior such as cutting, burning, or hitting myself. </string>
    <string name="PersonalityQuestion4">4. I have a significant and persistently unstable image or sense of myself, or of who I am or what I truly believe in.</string>
    <string name="PersonalityQuestion5">5. I have very suspicious ideas, and am even paranoid (falsely believe that others are plotting to cause me harm) or I experience episodes under stress when I feel that I, other people, or the situation is somewhat unreal.</string>
    <string name="PersonalityQuestion6">6. I engage in two or more self-damaging acts such as excessive spending, unsafe and inappropriate sexual conduct, substance abuse, reckless driving, and binge eating.</string>
    <string name="PersonalityQuestion7">7. I engage in frantic efforts to avoid real or imagined abandonment by people who are close to me.</string>


    <string name="SucidalityTestTitle">Sucidality Test</string>
    <string name="SucidalityQuestion1">1. Have you been feeling hopeless or helpless lately?</string>
    <string name="SucidalityQuestion2">2. Have you experienced a loss of interest in activities you used to enjoy?</string>
    <string name="SucidalityQuestion3">3. Do you often feel like a burden to others?</string>
    <string name="SucidalityQuestion4">4. Have you been experiencing significant changes in your sleep patterns (either sleeping too much or too little)?</string>
    <string name="SucidalityQuestion5">5. Have you been experiencing changes in your appetite or weight (either eating too much or too little)?</string>
    <string name="SucidalityQuestion6">6. Have you been feeling unusually fatigued or lacking in energy?</string>
    <string name="SucidalityQuestion7">7. Have you been isolating yourself from friends or family?</string>


    <string name="EatingDisorderTestTitle">Eating Disorder Test</string>
    <string name="EatingQuestion1">1. When you lose control over your eating, do you eat even though you are not hungry?</string>
    <string name="EatingQuestion2">2. Do you struggle to control when and how much you eat?</string>
    <string name="EatingQuestion3">3. When you lose control over your eating, do you eat more rapidly than you usually do?</string>
    <string name="EatingQuestion4">4. Do you find yourself eating more when you try to restrict how much you eat?</string>
    <string name="EatingQuestion5">5. When you lose control over your eating, do you eat more food than others would under similar circumstances?</string>
    <string name="EatingQuestion6">6. When you lose control over your eating, do you feel like you cannot stop eating once you\'ve started?</string>
    <string name="EatingQuestion7">7. When you cannot stop eating, do you eat so much that you feel uncomfortably full afterwards?</string>


    <string name="DissociationTestTitle">Dissociation Test</string>
    <string name="DissociationQuestion1">1.	Do you ever feel like you are disconnected from your thoughts, feelings, or surroundings?</string>
    <string name="DissociationQuestion2">2.	Have you experienced periods of time where you feel like you are watching yourself from outside your body?</string>
    <string name="DissociationQuestion3">3.	Do you ever feel like the world around you is unreal or dreamlike?</string>
    <string name="DissociationQuestion4">4.	Have you had moments where you could not remember significant parts of your day or events that happened?</string>
    <string name="DissociationQuestion5">5.	Do you ever find yourself suddenly in a place without remembering how you got there?</string>
    <string name="DissociationQuestion6">6.	Have you experienced a sense of being detached from your emotions, as if you are experiencing them from a distance?</string>
    <string name="DissociationQuestion7">7.	Do you ever feel like your body does not belong to you, or that parts of your body feel numb or not like your own?</string>


    <string name="ADHDTestTitle">ADHD Test</string>
    <string name="ADHDQuestion1">1. Do you tend to avoid or delay getting started on a new important task?</string>
    <string name="ADHDQuestion2">2. Do you find that the majority of your tasks (work/school assignments, etc.) are boring or repetitive, making them difficult to complete?</string>
    <string name="ADHDQuestion3">3. Do you find yourself making careless mistakes when engaged in something you feel is boring, repetitive, or difficult?</string>
    <string name="ADHDQuestion4">4. How often do you feel restless or fidgety?</string>
    <string name="ADHDQuestion5">5. Do you regularly fail to remember important appointments or obligations?</string>
    <string name="ADHDQuestion6">6. Do you have difficulty concentrating on people when they are speaking to you?</string>
    <string name="ADHDQuestion7">7. Do you frequently misplace things (or have difficulty finding them)?</string>


    <string name="SleepTitle">Sleep Test</string>
    <string name="SleepQuestion1">1. Do you have trouble falling asleep?</string>
    <string name="SleepQuestion2">2. Do you have trouble staying awake during the day?</string>
    <string name="SleepQuestion3">3. Do you get the amount of sleep you needed?</string>
    <string name="SleepQuestion4">4. Do you snore when you sleep?</string>
    <string name="SleepQuestion5">5. Do you take naps that are 5 minutes or longer during the day?</string>
    <string name="SleepQuestion6">6. Do you feel that your sleep was not quiet (e.g. feeling tense, moving restlessly, can\'t get comfortable)?</string>
    <string name="SleepQuestion7">7. Do you awaken short of breath or with a headache in the morning?</string>


</resources>